// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [

  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which verb is used to show possession?",
    answer: "have",
    options: [
    "there",
    "be",
    "have",
    "none of the above"
    ]
    },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which verb is used to describe the existence of something?",
    answer: "there to be",
    options: [
    "have",
    "do",
    "be",
    "there to be"
    ]
    },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "I _____ a book in my bag.",
    answer: "have",
    options: [
    "there is",
    "there are",
    "have",
    "be"
    ]
    },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "_____ a pen on the desk?",
    answer: "Is there",
    options: [
    "Are there",
    "Is there",
    "There is",
    "There are"
    ]
    },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "_____ any milk in the fridge?",
    answer: "Is there",
    options: [
    "Are there",
    "Is there",
    "There is",
    "There are"
    ]
    },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "I _____ a headache.",
    answer: "have",
    options: [
    "there is",
    "there are",
    "have",
    "be"
    ]
    },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "There _____ a party tonight.",
    answer: "is",
    options: [
    "are",
    "isn't",
    "aren't",
    "none of the above"
    ]
    },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "_____ any water in the bottle?",
    answer: "Is there",
    options: [
    "Are there",
    "Is there",
    "There is",
    "There are"
    ]
    },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "I _____ two brothers and one sister.",
    answer: "have",
    options: [
    "there is",
    "there are",
    "have",
    "be"
    ]
    },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "_____ a library near here?",
    answer: "Is there",
    options: [
    "Are there",
    "Is there",
    "There is",
    "There are"
    ]
    },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "There _____ some bread in the basket.",
    answer: "is",
    options: [
    "are",
    "isn't",
    "aren't",
    "none of the above"
    ]
    },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "_____ a hotel in this city?",
    answer: "Is there",
    options: [
    "Are there",
    "Is there",
    "There is",
    "There are"
    ]
    },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "I _____ a meeting at 10 am tomorrow.",
    answer: "have",
    options: [
    "there is",
    "there are",
    "have",
    "be"
    ]
    },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "_____ a movie theater in this area?",
    answer: "Is there",
    options: [
    "Are there",
    "Is there",
    "There is",
    "There are"
    ]
    },

    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "_____ any fruit juice in the fridge?",
      answer: "Is there",
      options: [
      "Are there",
      "Is there",
      "There is",
      "There are"
      ]
      }
];

/*
I need 3 English questions with 4 options each. The topic is: simple grammar questions for begginers. 
The following structure must be followed:

{
    numb: "number",
    question: "question goes here",
    answer: "correct answer goes here, exactly how it is in the option",
    options: [
    "option 1",
    "option 2",
    "option 3",
    "option 4"
    ]
    },

    */